(水月)さっさと その耳障りな
ダジャレヤローを➡
Let's get to it and
silence this irritating rapper.
黙らせてしまおうよ！
(サスケ)そのつもりだ！
I intend to.
It's not irritating...
♪♪(キラービー)「ダジャレじゃねえ
オシャレなライムじゃ コノヤロー アゥ アエー！」
It's cool rhythms and rhymes.
You fool! Ah! Yeah!!
(香燐)なんか マジ ムカツクな！
He's really...irritating!
He's got zero rapping talent!
コイツ ラップの才能ねえじゃん！
What?! You fool! You jerk!
♪♪「何だと！ コノヤロー バカヤロー！」
Will you shut up?!
うるせえ 黙れ！
The pain in my chest, baby!
Is like from your kicking, yo!
You're not running now, come on!
We're settling this score
'til I'm kicking, YEAH!
RHYME NOTES
I'm feeling good right now.
今は気分がいいぜ
最高のライムが書けた センキュー。
Just came up with
the greatest rhyme.
Thank you.
♪♪「だから 遊んでやるぜ
バカヤロー ベイベー！」
That's why I'll play with you...
You foolish baby!
Watch out, Sasuke!
This guy's used to handling blades!
気をつけて サスケ
コイツ 刀を使い慣れてる!!
ただの忍じゃないよ。
He's no ordinary ninja!
フフフ…。
オレ様のフック 感じさせてやるぜ！
I'll give you a taste of my hook.
The Eight-Tails vs. Sasuke
Wha--?
な…。
なんだ？ あの構えは。
What's with that stance?
Sasuke! Are you all right?!
サスケ！ 大丈夫か!?
What's with those moves?
なんだよ あの動き…
太刀筋が まるでよめない。
I can't read through
his line of attack.
《千鳥…。
Chidori?
ガード不可の千鳥刀か》
He plans to use
his indefensible Chidori Blade!
What?! He countered it?!
何!? ガードした!?
《アイツも
チャクラ流しを使えるのか!?》
He can stream his chakra too?!
Float... Float like a butterfly...!
♪♪「マイ！ 蝶のように舞い！」
♪♪「八尾 蜂のように刺す」
Eight-Tails! Sting like a bee!
Sasuke!
サスケ!!
And this is the finishing sting!
♪♪「そして これでトドメ刺す！」
《くっ… コイツも
ボクの苦手な雷遁を!?》
He also uses...
Lightning Style, which is my weakness.
Sasuke!
サスケ！
やばい。
This is bad...
ほら サスケ。
さっさと ウチに噛みつけ。
Here, Sasuke...
Hurry up and bite me!
ほら 早く。
Do it now!
あぁ～。
He funneled the Lightning Style
through his body
《雷遁を体に流して
攻撃の軌道をずらしたか。
and shifted the course of my attack.
致命傷は 避けたようだな。
He avoided a fatal injury...
で あの女がチャクラを吸わせて
回復させる能力か》
And...that woman possesses
the ability
to heal others by letting them
suck her chakra.
ハァ… ハァ…。
助かったぞ 香燐。
ああ…。
Thanks, Karin.
Sure...
サスケ ３人でやるよ。
Sasuke! Let's do this together!
はっきり言って この人
ムチャクチャ強いよね。
The fact is this guy is super strong.
殺さずってのは 考えず➡
We should go at him as if
we are trying to kill him, instead of not.
殺すつもりでいこう。
それで 死なない程度に
倒せるはずだよ。
That way we can probably take him
down without killing him.
こりゃあ バトルが長引きそうだぜ。
Looks like this battle is gonna drag on...
チェケラッチョ！
Check it out, yo!
かかったな。
Got you!
サスケ今だよ ボクごとやれ。
Sasuke, now! Just do the both of us!
千鳥！
Chidori!
(重吾)いない… どこだ？
Gone! Where is he?
♪♪「弱いくせに めんどくせえ」
So weak, yet so persistent...
I'm done playing,
now go home for some drinking! Yeah!
♪♪「遊びは終わり
帰って 水割り イェ～」
香燐！
わかってる！
- Karin!
- I know...
あそこだ！
Over there!
《感知タイプでもあるのか あの女》
That woman's also a sensory-type, eh?
しかたない。
Can't be helped...
Going with the eighth tail.
８本目だ！ ウィ～!!
《出たか…
同じだな あの時と…》
Here it comes...
It's the same as back then.
《ほぉ～
この８本目をかわしたのは➡
Hmm... He's the first to dodge
my eight-tails form
ブラザー以来だ》
since my brother.
Damn, he's going after the others!
クソッ！ そっちに！
♪♪「先に お前ら バラバラ」
First, you guys will be torn apart!
無事か！
Are you all right?
あぁ… なんとかな。
Yeah...more or less...
《確かに スピードも威力もある。
He definitely has speed and power.
だが 動きは直線的。
But he only moves in
a linear fashion.
My eyes should be able to
make them out.
この目なら
見切れないことはない。
香燐！ ヤツのチャクラを感じとって
行動を先読みしろ！
Karin! Read his chakra and
predict his movements!
ヤツの居場所は 常に把握して
オレに伝えるんだ！
Stay on him and keep me informed
of his location at all times!
それで 間に合うならな!!
That's if you can really keep up!
Sasuke!
サスケ!!
《その目 写輪眼！
Those eyes... The Sharingan!
Is this genjutsu?
幻術か… 体が動かない！》
I can't move my body.
うっ！
Lariat!
ラリアット!!
ウィ～!!
サスケ!!
Sasuke!
Wha--?!
な… 何だよ？ これ…。
What is this?
体の 首と胸の部分が➡
His neck and chest portion have
been blown off, organs and all.
内臓ごと ふっ飛んでる…。
ハァ… ハァ… ハァ…。
これは… もう…。
He's beyond our...
He is like my reincarnation.
((君麻呂 : 彼は ボクの
生まれ変わりのような存在だ))
待ってろ！
Hang in there!
香燐 いい オレがやる。
Karin, it's all right. I'll do it.
今のお前のチャクラじゃ 無理だろう。
The chakra you have now
can't deal with it.
何をする気だ!?
What do you intend to do?
I'll distribute my body and chakra to
Sasuke by merging with him.
サスケの体と同化して
オレのチャクラと 体を分け与える。
Since his body was compatible with
my curse mark, it should work.
オレの呪印と適合できた
サスケの体なら できるはずだ。
幻術を解くには
己のチャクラを乱して➡
In order to release the genjutsu,
I need a partner to disturb
my chakra and awaken me.
目を覚ましてくれる相棒が必要だ。
オレ様の相棒は オレの中の八尾。
My partner is
the Eight-Tails inside me.
尾獣をコントロールした人柱力に
幻術は効かねえ。
A genjutsu has no effect on
the Jinchuriki host,
which controls a Tailed Beast.
♪♪「お前らには 幻滅」
Your illusions I obliterate,
then you all I shall annihilate.
♪♪「そして お前ら 壊滅」
My true form of the Jinchuriki...
♪♪「人柱力である オレ様の本当の姿」
It's a monster, so watch it now,
♪♪「それは怪物 それを見物
人柱変化 イエ～イ」
Host Transformation, yeah...
♪♪「八尾でちびれ おチビ共」
Eight-Tails will pee your pants,
you lil' ants!
《このチャクラ… こんなのって
ありなのか？》
Such chakra...
Is this even possible?
これが 八尾。
That's the Eight-Tails?
牛とタコのバケモノ…。
An ox-octopus monster...
That's his true form?
それが ヤツの正体ってわけか。
♪♪「敵を刺す 敵刺すロングホーン」
To spear my foes,
my glorious longhorns!
ウィ～!!
《このチャクラ ありえない。
ここにいたら死ぬ！》
His chakra is off the scale...
We'll die if we stay here!
重吾 まだなのか？
Jugo, are you done yet?!
《よかった… サスケ》
Thank goodness... Sasuke...
気づいたか！
ほら さっさと起きろ。
You're conscious.
Come on, get up!
よし 重吾… え？
All right, Jugo... Huh?!
子供に？ なんで!?
He turned into a child?! Why?!
重吾…。
Jugo...
お前は死なせない。
君麻呂の形見だからな。
I won't let you die...
You're a memento of Kimimaro.
ほら早く！
２人とも逃げるぜ！
Come on! Hurry! We gotta run!
ウィ～!!
やっぱ 水遁系の忍だったか。
A Water-Style ninja... I knew it.
地の利を得たな!!
You have the advantage
of the terrain!
デヤ～！
ここは ボクがやる！
I'll take over from here!
今のうちに逃げろ！
Run while you can!
ウ～!!
水月…。
行くぞ サスケ。
Suigetsu...
Let's go, Sasuke.
ウオ～!!
Heh. Who would've thought...
《このボクが 何度も身を挺して
あんなヤツらをかばうなんてね》
that I'd end up sacrificing myself
to save their hides this often?
うお～!!
ここまでさせておいて 逃がすか!!
As if I'd let you get away after
what you've done, you fool, you jerk!
バカヤロー コノヤロー！
ウオ～!!
ヤバすぎるぞ アレ！
Th-That really doesn't look good.
まさか アレは キラービー様の…。
Could that be Lord Killer Bee's?!
何です？ 先輩。
Wh-What is it, Senpai?!
行くぞ！
はい！
- Let's go!
- Yes, sir!
こ… これは！
Th-That's...!
キラービー様
なんで 八尾のお姿に？
Lord Killer Bee...
Why has he transformed into
the Eight-Tails?!
あれほど
雷影様から止められていたのに。
And after all that lecturing
from Lord Raikage...
よく見てください！
誰かと戦ってます！
Look closely!
He's battling someone!
あの衣… 暁か？
Those robes...
Are they the Akatsuki?
アレが ユギトを連れ去った…。
The ones who kidnapped Yugito?
水月が こんなに…。
クソ… 逃げきれないぞ。
Suigetsu is wasted... Damn it!
We can't get away... What'll we do?!
どうすんだよ？
Here, Sasuke.
Hurry up and bite me!
((ほら サスケ
さっさと ウチに噛みつけ！
お前は死なせない。
I won't let you die...
君麻呂の形見だからな。
You're a memento of Kimimaro.
(ここは ボクがやる！
今のうちに逃げろ！))
I'll take over from here!
Run while you can!
ウィ～！
(香燐)くるぞ！
He's coming!
《天照！》
Amaterasu!
うわぁ～！
《こ… これが サスケの言っていた
消えない黒炎か！》
S-So those are the inextinguishable
black flames Sasuke spoke of!
グオ～！
《す… すげえ》
A-Awesome!
ぐあ～！
あっ…。
あ～っ！
香燐 走れ！
Karin, run!
あっ…。
クソ 黒炎が…。
Damn! The black flames!
香燐は もうダメだ。
オレたちも巻きぞえを食う前に➡
It's too late for Karin.
We need to get away before
we get caught too!
ここを いったん離れる！
待て 重吾。
- Wait, Jugo.
- No!
ダメだ！
Karin!
《香燐…》
うわっ… あ～！
こ… これは…。
Wh-What?
重吾 香燐を早く！
Jugo! Get Karin! Hurry!
やはり 黒炎が消えている…。
どういうことだ サスケ！
The black flames are extinguished...
What's going on, Sasuke?
《消せた…
あの天照の黒炎を…。
I was able to extinguish
the black flames of Amaterasu.
これが この万華鏡の瞳力なのか。
Are these the visual powers
of my Mangekyo Sharingan?!
それなら…》
In which case...
八尾…
かろうじて生きているようだ。
The Eight-Tails...
It seems he's barely alive.
これで 八尾を殺さずにすんだ…
さっさと連れていくぞ。
Then...we managed to take down
the Eight-Tails without killing him.
Let's grab him and go.
まさか…
あの キラービー様がやられた…。
No way...
Lord Killer Bee has been defeated?
そんな ウソでしょう…
助けますか？
I-It must be some mistake...
Shall we rescue him?
ヤツらは 暁のメンバーだ 早まるな。
They're Akatsuki members.
Don't be hasty.
ん… あれは！
何です!?
Huh?! That's...
What is it?!
うちはの家紋！
The Uchiha crest!
うちは？
オレたちは出しゃばるより➡
Uchiha?
Rather than taking action ourselves,
we'd better get word to Lord Raikage!
すぐに雷影様に
報告したほうが賢明だ。
弟がこんな目にあったとなったら
あの雷影様…。
If he hears what happened
to his younger brother...
Knowing Lord Raikage,
he won't be pleased at all.
黙ってませんね…。
だいぶ 体にきているようだな…。
You seem quite affected, physically.
大蛇丸の呪印も
なくなったあげく➡
E
イタチ戦での傷も
癒えていなかったからな…。
あぁ… ここまで追い込まれるとは
思ってもみなかったがな。
だが これで…。
(ナツ)ぶわぁ～ ぶぇ～。